<Publish>
  <ModId Value="74182" />
  <DisplayName Value="Addresses &amp; Names Mod" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Extends name generation systems." />
  <LongDescription># Addresses &amp; Names Mod for Cities Skylines 2
## _Name it all as you wish_

This mod is the successor of the CS1 homonimous mod. It allows changing vanilla methods of name generation to custom name sets.

You can find several name files at [Addresses Files repository at GitHub](https://github.com/klyte45/AddressesFiles). These files will work for both CS1 and CS2 versions of this mod.

**NOTICE:** 
- Surname files are not compatible with the CS2 version. To make them compatible, open the file and remove all text like `{0}` from the file.
- Road qualifier files aren't compatible with CS2.

## Current features

- Edit names of any clickable object in the editor (and save changes to send with the maps created)
- Change sources references for stations names and seeds for roads and districts names in the selected info panel
- In-game filename viewer, showing the weight of each word.
  - Words with a higher weight tends to appear more frequently
  - Raise word weight by creating several lines with same content in the name file.
- Organize your file names using subfolder in the names folder (NEW)
- Choose files to override name generation of:
  - Male cims
  - Female cims
  - Surnames (are last names as default, but may be inverted to follow oriental standard)
	- To use gendered surnames, in the surname files add the female and male version of the surname separated by a semicolon (;)
  - Dogs (NEW)
  - Roads (Global and by district)
  - Districts
- Roads qualifier rules editor
  - Use ingame UI to create several rules to differentiate streets, avenues, highways, etc by their characteristics
  - Very limited options to customization at this moment, might be enhanced later
- Use district and road names to name your public transport stations!

Now it's possible to setup the mod to generate up to 5 given names and up to 5 surnames! Notice that very large names might be truncated by game limitations... This feature may receive a tunning in future releases to be more configurable.

## Experimental mod warning!
This mod may cause issues in the game due their early stage of development. This may be updated in the future until the official platform PDXMods get done and released

## Support
The most up to date information about installation and known issues and bugs is at the forum topíc.</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/addresses-names-mod-for-cs2.1651551/" />
  <ModVersion Value="0.1.3.2" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
  <ChangeLog># v0.1.3r2 (25-DEC-24)
- Fixing Editor name text box not accepting typed data
- Fixing minor issues with checkboxes at EUIS screen</ChangeLog>
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\00_identifierEditor.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\01_GHImport.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\02_qualifiers.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\04_20241023_composeSurname.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\05_0mapEditor.jpg" />
  <Dependency Id="74151" ModVersion="" DisplayName="Extra UI Screens" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/klyte45/CS2-AddressesMod " />
  <ExternalLink Type="youtube" Url="https://www.youtube.com/Klyte45" />
  <ExternalLink Type="kofi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/klyte45" />
</Publish>